You now I think
maybe we're starting to
see just the little
beginnings of it you
in software encoding I
didn't see it within
Anthropic where you I
can look forward I
can kind look forward
to a time where
on the more junior
end and then on
the more intermediate end
we actually need less
and not more people
And you we're thinking
about how to deal
with that within Anthropic
in a you in
a sensible way
I you one to
five years as of
six months ago I
would stick with that
You if you kind
of you connect this
to what I said
before which is you
we might have AI
that's better than humans
at everything in you
maybe one to two
years maybe a little
longer than that those
don't seem to line
up The reason is
that there's this lag
and there's this replacement
thing right I know
that the labor market
is adaptable right It's
just like you 80
of people used to
do farming you got
automated and then they
became factory workers and
then knowledge workers So
you there is some
level of adaptability here
as well right We
should be economically sophisticated
about how the labor
market works But my
worry is as this
exponential keeps compounding and
I don't think it's
going to take that
long again somewhere between
a year and five
years it will overwhelm
our ability to adapt